<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Memberships on BrainSilo - Portland&#39;s Hackerspace </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/membership/index.xml</link>
    
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Members</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/membership/members</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/membership/members</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
    $(function($) {
      var json = &#34;http://api.meetup.com/2/profiles?group_id=8102912&amp;order=visited&amp;offset=0&amp;format=json&amp;page=200&amp;fields=membership_dues&amp;sig_id=70219012&amp;sig=0f85d99b4ec83af7df850e456290db7ebe9c5b62&amp;callback=?&#34;;
      var members = $.getJSON(json,function(x) {
        console.log(x.results);
        var paid_members = _.filter(x.results, function(m) {return m.membership_dues.period_status == &#34;paid&#34; || m.membership_dues.exempt == true; });
        _.forEach(paid_members, function(m) {
          var s = &#34;&lt;div&gt;&#34; + 
          var o = $(&#34;&lt;div&gt;&#34;).append(m.name);
          $(&#34;div.main-content.container&#34;).append(o);
        });
      });
    });
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership Agreement &amp; Liability Release</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/membership/agreement</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/membership/agreement</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in becoming a member, please read our &lt;strong&gt;Membership Agreement&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Liability Release&lt;/strong&gt; all the way through and make sure that you can abide by them as a member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Membership Agreement&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shop Hours:&lt;/strong&gt; BrainSilo will be open to members 24/7, except for occasional special events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payment&lt;/strong&gt;: If you are not using BrainSilo&amp;rsquo;s online payment service (via meetup.com), then monthly fees are due on the 1st of the month, and late after the 5th.  Memberships can be put on hiatus and revived at a later month but this must be communicated in writing with &lt;a href=&#34;/about/leadership&#34;&gt;BrainSilo leadership&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volunteering&lt;/strong&gt;: All members are encouraged, but not required, to volunteer at least 3 hours per month in order to benefit, grow, and provide upkeep to BrainSilo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cleaning and Lockup&lt;/strong&gt;: All members are responsible for cleaning up after themselves including properly storing projects. When leaving for the day, members must lockup the space if they are the last ones out. This includes locking doors, turning off lights and power, and taking out any full or odorous garbage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Ethical and Behavioral Guidelines&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BrainSilo does not have a &amp;ldquo;Safe Space Policy&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Anti-harassment policy&amp;rdquo; or similar.  Instead, we presume that our members are adults, and assume they can act as such.  BrainSilo&amp;rsquo;s goal is to provide a productive environment for work, learning, and creativity for its members; we do not act as parents, tell you what you should wear, or tell you what language to use or not to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that said, we do have some general best practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Individual Safety: Consider all posted signs and literature pertaining to safe use of our facilities. These include but are not limited to: signs regarding appropriate shop clothing and protective gear, techniques for safe equipment use, material-specific precautions for equipment, and machine tool lockouts. Do not use equipment you are not comfortable with or trained to use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shared Safety: In a shared and open facility like ours, it is possible for less experienced members to operate equipment dangerously without knowing it. Please stay on the lookout for unsafe behavior, and approach and offer feedback to fellow members if you believe they are working unsafely. Please notify staff immediately if you believe any piece of equipment or infrastructure to be unsafe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respectful Behavior: In both face to face and electronic interactions, behave respectfully, courteously, and professionally to your fellow members. Though we greatly value free speech, verbal discrimination, harassment, or hate speech that is directed at another individual is strongly discouraged; any physical harassment is one of the few grounds for expulsion from the space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tolerance of Feedback: Please be open to constructive feedback from fellow members, especially as it pertains to safe use of our equipment and disrespectful communication or behavior.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Liability Release&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In consideration for your being permitted to participate in the activities of BrainSilo, you agree to and accept the following waiver and release:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ASSUMPTION OF RISK:&lt;/strong&gt; I acknowledge that inherent risks, dangers and hazards and such exist when using power and hand tools commonly used in electronics construction, fabrication, software design and other technology or art related activities. Participation in such activities and/or the use of equipment associated with technology or art design, manufacture and experimentation may result in injury, illness, death or damage to personal property. These risks and dangers may be caused by other participants, members or by accidents, acts of nature or other causes. Risks and dangers may arise from foreseeable or unforeseeable causes including, but not limited to electrocution, burns, impalement, injury from slips or falls, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELEASE OF LIABILITY:&lt;/strong&gt; I fully assume all risks associated with participation in events and exempt and release BrainSilo, its members, officers, agents, and board members from action whatsoever arising out of any damage, loss or injury to myself or the my property while upon the premises or using any equipment of the organization or while participating in any of the activities contemplated by this agreement whether such loss, damage, or injury results from the negligence of the corporation, its members, agents, or from some other cause.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVENANT NOT TO SUE:&lt;/strong&gt; I agree never to institute any suit or action at law otherwise against BrainSilo, its members, officers, board members, agents, nor to initiate or any way assist the prosecution of any claim for damages or course of action which I, my heirs, executors or administrators hereafter may have by reason of injury to the person of myself or to my property arising from the activities contemplated by this agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THIRD PARTY INDEMNIFICATION:&lt;/strong&gt; I will indemnify, save and hold harmless BrainSilo, its members, officers, board members, or agents from any and all losses, claims, actions, or proceedings of every kind and character which may be presented or initiated by any other persons or organizations and which arise directly or indirectly from the actions of the member while engaged in the activities contemplated by this agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;By entering or remaining on the premises of BrainSilo, you hereby acknowledge that you have CAREFULLY read all of the provisions above, fully understand the terms and conditions expressed there, and do freely choose acceptance of the provisions of the foregoing paragraphs relating to assumption of risk, release of liability, covenant not to sue, and third party indemnification.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Member</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/membership</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/membership</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;BrainSilo is open for membership!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before applying for membership, please read the following&lt;/strong&gt; pages/sections:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/status/&#34;&gt;Our current status&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/space/&#34;&gt;Our space&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/membership/agreement/&#34;&gt;Our membership agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, membership is &lt;strong&gt;$40/month&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are encouraged volunteer to help setup and run events and meetups, help us clean, or improve the space in some way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;key reasons to become a member of BrainSilo&lt;/strong&gt; include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple work benches to work on projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;24/7 access, using an electroinc keypad&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use our wifi and our little kitchenette and our heating and AC&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member discount on classes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to our growing list of tools and supplies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our large library of books&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access any of our new equipment (3D printers, CNC machines, etc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Host your own meetups at BrainSilo!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;And most importantly, being part of a group of people who are keeping Portland&amp;rsquo;s oldest hackerspace running&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds like something you&amp;rsquo;d love to be a part of, please join our &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.meetup.com/BrainSilo&#34;&gt;Meetup Group&lt;/a&gt;, and then &lt;a href=&#34;https://secure.meetup.com/BrainSilo/pay_dues/&#34;&gt;pay your member dues&lt;/a&gt; when you do!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen our space yet but are interested in being one of our members, &lt;a href=&#34;/calendar/&#34;&gt;come to a meetup&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt; to setup a tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Membership FAQ&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;What Equipment Do You Have?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/about/equipment/&#34;&gt;Equipment page&lt;/a&gt; for an updated list of our equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;What Volunteer Commitment Are You Looking For?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t have a hard requirement on volunteering. We want members to take the initiative to find things that need to be done at BrainSilo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the trash needs to be taken out, then take it out. If a station is messy, clean it up. If you need a piece of equipment, then help us acquire it. If you want to start doing X at BrainSilo, then make it happen (as long as it&amp;rsquo;s relatively safe and legal)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_3&#34;&gt;What Membership Commitment Do You Require?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this time, we don&amp;rsquo;t require any membership commitment though we ask you to give us a heads up if you&amp;rsquo;re going to cancel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_4&#34;&gt;What Is The Cancellation Policy?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can cancel at any time with no penalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;d like to cancel your membership, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:admin@brainsilo.org&#34;&gt;email us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_5&#34;&gt;Are There Any Setup Fees&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, there are no setup fees to become a member. We may decide to change this in the future if we deem it necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_6&#34;&gt;Are There Any Other Fees?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not at the moment&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_7&#34;&gt;Guests&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our current guest policy is that any member may bring in guests, but guests are encouraged to become members if they are utilizing the space often - ideas for incentivizing this switch are welcome. Guests must be accompanied by a member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;toc_8&#34;&gt;Members of other Hackerspaces&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a member of a hackerspace that is not in the metro area, then you are probably welcome to use our space while you are in town - just &lt;a href=&#34;/contact/&#34;&gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are also open to the idea of formal reciprocal membership with other hackerspaces.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>